http://www.amergold.com/about-age/privacy-policy.php

Customer reviews
Why Partner with AGE?
Call 800-613-9323
(0)
Home > About AGE > AGE Privacy Policy
AGE Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the amergold.com website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
We purge this information from our webserver within 2 or 3 days of receiving it.
We do not collect credit card numbers.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when you place an order or request information only to aid in fulfilling that order or request. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use email addresses for internal marketing and customer service only. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and marketing materials.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We do not collect credit card numbers.
reCAPTCHA v3
To fight spam and abuse on our site, AGE has implemented reCAPTCHA v3 from Google to verify that you are not a robot when you submit forms. The use of re-CAPTCHA v3 is subject to Google's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (800) 613-9323 or send us an email at info@amergold.com.
